<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed>
 <title>Planet Openbox</title>
 <link>http://icculus.org/openbox/discuss-planet.shtml</link>
 <description>Blog entries from around the Openbox planet</description>
 <item>
  <name>Og Maciel</name>
  <nick>OgMaciel</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/ogmaciel.png</image>
  <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee/~3/TlCYU55f4zs/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m the proud father of two voracious young readers! From very early on I was able to instill into my daughters the pleasure of reading books. They also happen to be girly girls, so while most kids ask for toys and video games for their birthdays, mine ask for books and clothes/shoes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During third grade my oldest daughter happened to pick up &amp;#8220;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.heatherdakota.com/4.html&quot;&gt;Emma&amp;#8217;s very busy week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#8221; by &lt;strong&gt;Heather Dakota&lt;/strong&gt; from her school&amp;#8217;s library and just couldn&amp;#8217;t put it down! I believe that throughout the entire third grade she must have borrowed this book at least &lt;strong&gt;6 times&lt;/strong&gt;! As a young kid, I remember I could read some books that I really enjoyed over and over, enjoying it every single time as if I were reading it for the first time. She must have gotten this from me. &lt;img src=&quot;http://www.ogmaciel.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif&quot; alt=&quot;:)&quot; /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So now with the Summer break fast approaching she has asked me to buy&lt;br /&gt;
her own copy of the book. Again, I usually get all of my books from the public library but those I fall in love with, I just got to have them, so she must have gotten it from me too! I sat down in front of the computer and searched on &lt;strong&gt;Amazon&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Barnes and Noble&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Borders&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Books on Press&lt;/strong&gt;, etc, but just could not find a single reference or a way to buy &amp;#8220;Emma&amp;#8217;s very busy week&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I did what everyone does when in doubt and spent some time &amp;#8216;Googling&amp;#8217; around until I came across &lt;strong&gt;Heather Dakota&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;#8217;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.heatherdakota.com/index.html&quot;&gt;web site&lt;/a&gt;. Feeling that I had already exhausted my options, I figured I&amp;#8217;d drop her an email and see if she could help us find a place where we could buy the book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That same day I was pleasantly surprised to receive an email from Heather with a generous offer: she happened to have an extra copy of the book at her house and asked me if I&amp;#8217;d mind if she sent it autographed to my daughter! Better yet, she was meeting the illustrator the very next day and said she would also get it autographed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I profusely thanked her for the offer and decided I would not break the news to my daughter and see how  she would react when she received the package in the mail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ogmaciel.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/dscn0262.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;&quot;Emma's very busy week&quot; book&quot; src=&quot;http://www.ogmaciel.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/dscn0262-300x225.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;Emma's very busy week&quot; book&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;225&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Emma&amp;#39;s very busy week&quot; book&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Needless to say, she was in heaven when she received the package yesterday!!! The book was promptly devoured while I took my dog to training class and she&amp;#8217;s planning to read it again today!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you Heather for making my daughter&amp;#8217;s day! I thank you from the bottom of my heart and we are all looking forward to your next book!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=TlCYU55f4zs:qeVRYA4z2VU:yIl2AUoC8zA&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?d=yIl2AUoC8zA&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=TlCYU55f4zs:qeVRYA4z2VU:V_sGLiPBpWU&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?i=TlCYU55f4zs:qeVRYA4z2VU:V_sGLiPBpWU&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=TlCYU55f4zs:qeVRYA4z2VU:7Q72WNTAKBA&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?d=7Q72WNTAKBA&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=TlCYU55f4zs:qeVRYA4z2VU:F7zBnMyn0Lo&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?i=TlCYU55f4zs:qeVRYA4z2VU:F7zBnMyn0Lo&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=TlCYU55f4zs:qeVRYA4z2VU:qj6IDK7rITs&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?d=qj6IDK7rITs&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee/~4/TlCYU55f4zs&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>Emma’s Very Busy Week</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.ogmaciel.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Journal of an Open Sourcee</feedtitle>
  <id>ead63516aeee46f552b50115be8abc82</id>
  <date>1275678053</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Og Maciel</name>
  <nick>OgMaciel</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/ogmaciel.png</image>
  <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee/~3/3c-IyOBMG_s/</link>
  <text>&lt;a href=&quot;http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1143/1369658074_a56ad5bad6_m_d.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;Sad Trombone&quot; src=&quot;http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1143/1369658074_a56ad5bad6_m_d.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sad Trombone&quot; width=&quot;240&quot; height=&quot;171&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sad Trombone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After several weeks agonizing over how to afford a trip to attend &lt;strong&gt;GUADEC 2010&lt;/strong&gt;, I have finally arrived at the conclusion that I won&amp;#8217;t be able to make it. Due to my current financial situation and obligations as a father of two, it would be unrealistic to hop on a plane and go to this event right now for me. Unfortunately none of the organizations I approached were able to offer me any type of financial support, understandable due to today&amp;#8217;s economy issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to thank the amazing crew behind the &lt;strong&gt;GNOME Travel Committee&lt;/strong&gt; for a very generous offer and for being so patient and allowing me to take a bit of time to make my decision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also want to thank the &lt;strong&gt;organizers&lt;/strong&gt; for choosing my presentation and keeping me updated with the tentative schedule for the event. I&amp;#8217;m really sorry I won&amp;#8217;t be able to present it and I can only hope that someone else can fill in the vacancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, I wish you all a wonderful event and I will be watching from the sidelines for the many amazing things that are sure to come out of GUADEC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=3c-IyOBMG_s:mchQdNQxwVE:yIl2AUoC8zA&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?d=yIl2AUoC8zA&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=3c-IyOBMG_s:mchQdNQxwVE:V_sGLiPBpWU&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?i=3c-IyOBMG_s:mchQdNQxwVE:V_sGLiPBpWU&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=3c-IyOBMG_s:mchQdNQxwVE:7Q72WNTAKBA&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?d=7Q72WNTAKBA&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=3c-IyOBMG_s:mchQdNQxwVE:F7zBnMyn0Lo&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?i=3c-IyOBMG_s:mchQdNQxwVE:F7zBnMyn0Lo&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=3c-IyOBMG_s:mchQdNQxwVE:qj6IDK7rITs&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?d=qj6IDK7rITs&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</text>
  <title>Not Going to GUADEC 2010</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.ogmaciel.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Journal of an Open Sourcee</feedtitle>
  <id>e18185e58ebfb6eadb09d33063b6cffb</id>
  <date>1275602913</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>K Mandla</name>
  <nick>KMandla</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://kmandla.wordpress.com/2010/06/03/compiling-effortlessly-sort-of/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;It took me a while, but I finally ironed out my upgrade from kernel 2.6.30.7 to 2.6.34 this morning, on my &lt;a href=&quot;http://kmandla.wordpress.com/hardware#FMV-5120&quot;&gt;Pentium machine&lt;/a&gt;. Ordinarily I don&amp;#8217;t wait so long to make a jump, but things were going very well with 2.6.30.7, and since there is rarely any good reason to shift up, I let it stagnate for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But fear of obsolescence is a powerful thing, and realizing I had a kernel that dated back the better part of a year made me a little queasy. I know in the back of my mind that a 14-year-old machine has little to benefit between a kernel written in September 2009 and one written a few weeks ago, but it seemed worth the effort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not that it was a huge effort though. Usually I roll configuration between kernels with &lt;code&gt;make oldconfig&lt;/code&gt;, but this time I started from a clean page, and pruned out all the unnecessary parts. It took me a little while to fine-tune the framebuffer and a network parts, and the sound was the last thing I needed to fix. And now it&amp;#8217;s done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The odd part of the entire experience, and the reason why I mention it here, is that while the machine is slowly and faithfully correcting the modules I set, there&amp;#8217;s no slowdown or lag or performance hit. That&amp;#8217;s strange to me because on other hardware, for example my long-running &lt;a href=&quot;http://kmandla.wordpress.com/2009/10/02/so-long-old-friend/&quot;&gt;Inspiron&lt;/a&gt;, compiling or building a kernel more or less precluded using the machine outside of very trivial tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But this Pentium barely notices. Memory use peaks around 22-29Mb (alongside all the other software I normally run) and the CPU is pegged at 100 percent of course, but I can still type at normal speed, switch windows in screen or ttys at the console, manage remote systems with ssh, etc., etc., and not notice any stutter or lapse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wonder why that is?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, this is all moot point because it still takes 20 minutes to compile a single sound module, and most of a day and night to build an entire kernel. Praising it for not lagging while it meanders through the chore of building new software is like praising a snail for traveling in a straight line for a day. You&amp;#8217;re still frighteningly slow, and hardly covered any distance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it does mean that troubleshooting is a little easier, even if it takes longer. I can wait 20 minutes for a module to build, see if it works, and then go back to what I was doing without waiting or needing to switch machines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And all that being said, if there are a large number of packages to update or if there is a particularly large program to build (such as gcc), I yank the drive and connect it over USB to &lt;a href=&quot;http://kmandla.wordpress.com/hardware#X60s&quot;&gt;the fast computer&lt;/a&gt;. That&amp;#8217;s why I bought the fast one, and I&amp;#8217;m not such a glutton for punishment that I have to build software for days and days at 120Mhz. There are limits to my fanaticism. &lt;img src=&quot;http://s.wordpress.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_twisted.gif&quot; alt=&quot;:twisted:&quot; /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gocomments/kmandla.wordpress.com/4515/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/comments/kmandla.wordpress.com/4515/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godelicious/kmandla.wordpress.com/4515/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/delicious/kmandla.wordpress.com/4515/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gostumble/kmandla.wordpress.com/4515/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/stumble/kmandla.wordpress.com/4515/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godigg/kmandla.wordpress.com/4515/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/digg/kmandla.wordpress.com/4515/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/goreddit/kmandla.wordpress.com/4515/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/reddit/kmandla.wordpress.com/4515/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://stats.wordpress.com/b.gif?host=kmandla.wordpress.com&amp;blog=353512&amp;post=4515&amp;subd=kmandla&amp;ref=&amp;feed=1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>Compiling effortlessly … sort of</title>
  <feedurl>http://kmandla.wordpress.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Motho ke motho ka botho</feedtitle>
  <id>51a380a2255b6ba26b5710c4a1ae5562</id>
  <date>1275538930</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>K Mandla</name>
  <nick>KMandla</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://kmandla.wordpress.com/2010/06/02/the-code-monkey-script-project/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://wiki.ubuntu.com/tom.swartz07&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tom Swartz&lt;/a&gt; is heading up a small project called Code Monkey, which collects useful scripts into a package. As it stands there are about 10 small scripts in Code Monkey, ranging from bash one-liners, to python scripts that inject Google Reader subscriptions into conky, to a world sunlight map wallpaper fetcher. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scripts aren&amp;#8217;t necessarily intended for command-line only use, although one or two, like the rsync backup script, could run either in a terminal emulator or completely free of a graphical environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tom is looking for suggestions or ideas, and if you have one you&amp;#8217;d like to submit (or if you just want to see what he has collected already), you could contact him through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://edge.launchpad.net/codemonkey/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Launchpad page for Code Monkey&lt;/a&gt;, or probably catch his eye with a post to &lt;a href=&quot;http://ubuntuforums.org/showthread.php?t=1499303&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;this thread&lt;/a&gt; in the Ubuntu Forums.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gocomments/kmandla.wordpress.com/4512/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/comments/kmandla.wordpress.com/4512/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godelicious/kmandla.wordpress.com/4512/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/delicious/kmandla.wordpress.com/4512/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gostumble/kmandla.wordpress.com/4512/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/stumble/kmandla.wordpress.com/4512/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godigg/kmandla.wordpress.com/4512/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/digg/kmandla.wordpress.com/4512/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/goreddit/kmandla.wordpress.com/4512/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/reddit/kmandla.wordpress.com/4512/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://stats.wordpress.com/b.gif?host=kmandla.wordpress.com&amp;blog=353512&amp;post=4512&amp;subd=kmandla&amp;ref=&amp;feed=1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>The Code Monkey script project</title>
  <feedurl>http://kmandla.wordpress.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Motho ke motho ka botho</feedtitle>
  <id>a7b9cf2e6542961b1edf1068d411c8d8</id>
  <date>1275459431</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>K Mandla</name>
  <nick>KMandla</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://kmandla.wordpress.com/2010/06/01/three-floppy-based-distros/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;This might sound strange, but I generally don&amp;#8217;t endorse the floppy distros that are still available here and there on the Internet, and as a general rule, still work fine. I don&amp;#8217;t hold any prejudice toward them, but I find that they&amp;#8217;re out of date, intended for specific hardware arrangements, or just a bit too &amp;#8230; personalized. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can vouch for two or three as possibilities though, if you&amp;#8217;re working with hardware that is terrifically old, or extremely underpowered. Usually these are offered as solutions to machines with very, very little memory (4Mb or 8Mb) , and if that&amp;#8217;s the case they will probably be lifesavers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.micheleandreoli.it/mulinux/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;muLinux&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is mentioned quite often as a possibility for older machines, and actually, if you have a working CD drive, this might be a better solution for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had to use the ISO version of muLinux 14.0 because the installer scripts packaged in the floppy version wouldn&amp;#8217;t run for me on an Arch-based system. The ISO version was no disappointment though, and technically you&amp;#8217;ll probably get more in that 68Mb than you would from floppy after floppy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;muLinux has several versions with an array of add-ons that will get you closer to what you want the machine to do. Everything is text-driven from the startup, but there is support for an early graphical desktop, and the console system has a lot of software that you&amp;#8217;ll probably find useful. Once it&amp;#8217;s up and running, it can clone itself to a hard drive, and if you cross your fingers, it will boot up into a native system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#8217;s still rather old though, with the 2.0.36 kernel and gcc 2.7.2.1. If you install it you might have some luck bringing everything up to current, but that might be a huge, uphill task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a strictly floppy-based distro, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.volny.cz/basiclinux/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BasicLinux&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a good example. One floppy boots the system, and the other is a compressed file tree. Memory use is trivial, with only about 4Mb or so taken up. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazingly this also has a graphical desktop that will give you JWM and a few utilities, to include (of all things) a slideshow presentation tool (works great on &lt;a href=&quot;http://kmandla.wordpress.com/hardware#FMV-5120&quot;&gt;this machine&lt;/a&gt;, too). So if you really want to score some geek points, you can boot this up on the dual-core laptop in your office, and give the budget report on the overhead projector with BasicLinux. &lt;img src=&quot;http://s.wordpress.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_eek.gif&quot; alt=&quot;:shock:&quot; /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#8217;s still quite a bit out of date though, so it&amp;#8217;s usefulness beyond budget meetings, troubleshooting or data recovery is shaky &amp;#8230; and considering that much has changed in file systems and hardware, a 2.2.26 kernel might not be able to get to that hard drive like you want. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, this one has strong PCMCIA support, so if you&amp;#8217;re riding the information wave on an old NE2000 network card, like I am, then this will be great for checking e-mail or looking up technical specifications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably the one floppy distro that I would consider keeping around is &lt;a href=&quot;http://blueflops.sourceforge.net/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;blueflops&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and it&amp;#8217;s for that same reason &amp;#8212; hardware support. Another two-floppy adventure, this one lists quite a few network cards as options, particularly for desktops. And since blueflops has the 2.6.18-ck1 kernel, I would almost consider using that as a jumping-off point for upgrading to a current kernel. Almost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;blueflops says it will run on an i386 with 8Mb and swap, and I&amp;#8217;ve tried it on machines with only 16Mb and gotten fair results. The software list isn&amp;#8217;t as long as some of the others, but it will probably get you online and from there, you can decide on your direction. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For my own part, I have had much better luck getting older machines running with customized, transplanted systems built with newer software, than by bending someone else&amp;#8217;s floppy-based system to my will. There&amp;#8217;s no reason not to try these things though, since it could possibly be what keeps a machine out of a landfill. And hey, maybe a current, up-to-date floppy-based distro can be my next project. &amp;#8230; &lt;img src=&quot;http://s.wordpress.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_rolleyes.gif&quot; alt=&quot;:roll:&quot; /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gocomments/kmandla.wordpress.com/4510/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/comments/kmandla.wordpress.com/4510/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godelicious/kmandla.wordpress.com/4510/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/delicious/kmandla.wordpress.com/4510/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gostumble/kmandla.wordpress.com/4510/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/stumble/kmandla.wordpress.com/4510/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godigg/kmandla.wordpress.com/4510/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/digg/kmandla.wordpress.com/4510/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/goreddit/kmandla.wordpress.com/4510/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/reddit/kmandla.wordpress.com/4510/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://stats.wordpress.com/b.gif?host=kmandla.wordpress.com&amp;blog=353512&amp;post=4510&amp;subd=kmandla&amp;ref=&amp;feed=1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>Three floppy-based distros</title>
  <feedurl>http://kmandla.wordpress.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Motho ke motho ka botho</feedtitle>
  <id>cc6e7e1855d5968397e3c53b68ef5b99</id>
  <date>1275361430</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Akkana Peck</name>
  <nick>akk</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://shallowsky.com/blog/writing/kdenlive2.html</link>
  <text>I've been so busy with
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.libregraphicsmeeting.org/2010/&quot;&gt;Libre Graphics
Meeting&lt;/a&gt; -- a whirlwind of GIMP caucuses, open source graphics,
free art and sharing of ideas --
that I forgot to notice that part 2 of my kdenlive
article was up on Linux Planet.
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.linuxplanet.com/linuxplanet/tutorials/7079/1/&quot;&gt;Making
Movies in Linux with Kdenlive, part 2: Spice up Those Kdenlive Videos&lt;/a&gt;.</text>
  <title>Kdenlive part 2: adding transitions, sounds and titles to your movies</title>
  <feedurl>http://shallowsky.com/blog</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Shallow Thoughts</feedtitle>
  <id>d10c23329fa7ab4a5cd38d0421c0dd7d</id>
  <date>1275230700</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Og Maciel</name>
  <nick>OgMaciel</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/ogmaciel.png</image>
  <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee/~3/qh_V0J3GBRM/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;Week in Review&quot; src=&quot;http://bit.ly/DogReview&quot; alt=&quot;Week in Review&quot; width=&quot;286&quot; height=&quot;307&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;﻿﻿Here’s what happened this week:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;Permanent Link to The Maze Runner&quot; rel=&quot;bookmark&quot; href=&quot;http://www.ogmaciel.com/?p=1079&quot;&gt;The Maze Runner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This past March I started a new routine to my Sunday mornings: shortly after breakfast with the kids, I flip my laptop open and start reading the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/pages/books/index.html&quot;&gt;Books&lt;/a&gt; section[...]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;Permanent Link to Django Developer Kit 1.2.1&quot; rel=&quot;bookmark&quot; href=&quot;http://www.ogmaciel.com/?p=1089&quot;&gt;Django Developer Kit 1.2.1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have just released the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rpath.org/web/project/djangodevkit&quot;&gt;Django Developer Kit 1.2.1&lt;/a&gt; appliance to match with the release of &lt;a href=&quot;http://djangoproject.com&quot;&gt;Django&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;1.2.1&lt;/strong&gt;! Check this &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.djangoproject.com/weblog/2010/may/24/121/&quot;&gt;page&lt;/a&gt; for[...]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;Permanent Link to For The Win!&quot; rel=&quot;bookmark&quot; href=&quot;http://www.ogmaciel.com/?p=1084&quot;&gt;For The Win!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday I was lucky enough to have the chance of attending a book reading (well, a passage actually) by &lt;a href=&quot;http://craphound.com/&quot;&gt;Cory Doctorow&lt;/a&gt;! The event took place at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flyleafbooks.com/&quot;&gt;Flyleaf Books&lt;/a&gt; right here in&lt;strong&gt;Chapel Hill&lt;/strong&gt;, a charming independent book store[...]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;Permanent Link to Django 1.2 E-Commerce&quot; rel=&quot;bookmark&quot; href=&quot;http://www.ogmaciel.com/?p=1092&quot;&gt;Django 1.2 E-Commerce&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just received my complimentary copy of the book “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.packtpub.com/django-1-2-e-commerce-build-powerful-applications/book?utm_source=ogmaciel.com&amp;utm_medium=bookrev&amp;utm_content=blog&amp;utm_campaign=mdb_003454&quot;&gt;Django 1.2 E-Commerce&lt;/a&gt;” from &lt;a href=&quot;http://packtpub.com&quot;&gt;Packt Publishing&lt;/a&gt;! From the book’s overview[...]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=qh_V0J3GBRM:tLjkbsTLkdI:yIl2AUoC8zA&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?d=yIl2AUoC8zA&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=qh_V0J3GBRM:tLjkbsTLkdI:V_sGLiPBpWU&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?i=qh_V0J3GBRM:tLjkbsTLkdI:V_sGLiPBpWU&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=qh_V0J3GBRM:tLjkbsTLkdI:7Q72WNTAKBA&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?d=7Q72WNTAKBA&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=qh_V0J3GBRM:tLjkbsTLkdI:F7zBnMyn0Lo&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?i=qh_V0J3GBRM:tLjkbsTLkdI:F7zBnMyn0Lo&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?a=qh_V0J3GBRM:tLjkbsTLkdI:qj6IDK7rITs&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee?d=qj6IDK7rITs&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/JournalOfAnOpenSourcee/~4/qh_V0J3GBRM&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>Week in Review: May 24th – May 28th, 2010</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.ogmaciel.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Journal of an Open Sourcee</feedtitle>
  <id>7c56749e42b8df6ff64a11d3d66ec566</id>
  <date>1275159603</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Philip Newborough</name>
  <nick></nick>
  <image>rss/heads/philip.png</image>
  <link>http://crunchbang.org/archives/2010/05/28/my-dad-is-a-linux-user/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Foreword: Thank you to everybody who commented on my previous post, &amp;#34;&lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/archives/2010/05/23/dear-lazyweb-please-help-persuade-my-dad-to-move-to-linux/ &quot; title=&quot;Dear LazyWeb, please help persuade my dad to move to Linux&quot;&gt;Dear LazyWeb, please help persuade my dad to move to Linux&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#34; &amp;#8212; I really was not expecting so many helpful and constructive comments and I was slightly overwhelmed by the response. So, thank you to everyone who responded and helped to convince my dad to move to Linux, you rock!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I installed &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.linuxmint.com/ &quot; title=&quot;Linux Mint&quot;&gt;Linux Mint&lt;/a&gt; on my dad&amp;#39;s laptop. With the exception of a couple of bits of poorly supported hardware, the installation went without a hitch. I think my dad was genuinely pleased with his new Linux installation and he commented that it was definitely faster than the old Windows XP installation, he added that he thought it looked fairly easy to use too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, before performing the installation, I evaluated both the latest releases of &lt;a href=&quot;http:www.ubuntu.com &quot; title=&quot;Ubuntu Linux&quot;&gt;Ubuntu&lt;/a&gt; and Linux Mint in live sessions. I used both sessions for about half a day each and I came to the conclusion that my dad would probably be more comfortable using Linux Mint. I have no real scientific evidence to support my conclusion, but I figured that because my dad had always used Windows, he would prefer Mint&amp;#39;s default set-up. Mint also had a few other things going for it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It came pre-installed with a bunch of media codecs and Flash support. I know this is only a quick install of the &amp;#34;ubuntu-restricted-extras&amp;#34; package on Ubuntu, but it was nice for me not to have to do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mint did not come with &lt;a href=&quot;http://f-spot.org/ &quot; title=&quot;F-Spot&quot;&gt;F-Spot&lt;/a&gt;, at least I am pretty sure it did not. So, it was easy to install &lt;a href=&quot;http://yorba.org/shotwell/ &quot; title=&quot;Open source photo manager for GNOME&quot;&gt;Shotwell&lt;/a&gt;. My dad takes a lot of photos and Shotwell seems like a really nice photo management application; it is quick, stylish and easy to use. I think my dad was rather impressed with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know this is subjective, but Mint just looked more professional. The default theme and wallpaper is very stylish and it made Ubuntu look rather garish in comparison, even with its new look. Again, I know this is subjective and only a cosmetic issue, but I did not want to spend any time modifying themes, button placements and icons etcetera, so Mint won.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, and somewhat obviously, Linux Mint is effectively Ubuntu, but with some additional goodness, so there was no logical reason not to choose it for my dad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regarding the two bits of poorly supported hardware, the first was my dad&amp;#39;s Microsoft LifeCam webcam. My parents use &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.skype.com/ &quot; title=&quot;Skype&quot;&gt;Skype&lt;/a&gt; to make video calls to their grandchildren, so it was important to make sure this worked. I managed to get video working with the LifeCam and Skype, but it was a fugly hack and anyway, I could not get the built-in microphone to work. So, I popped out and purchased a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.logitech.com/en-gb/webcam_communications/webcams/devices/5865 &quot; title=&quot;Logitech C200 webcam&quot;&gt;Logitech C200 webcam&lt;/a&gt;, which worked out of the box, result. The second bit of dodgy hardware was a Lexmark printer, which I completely failed to get working. I have advised my dad on purchasing a &lt;a href=&quot;http://ur1.ca/03uj6 &quot; title=&quot;HP Deskjet D1660 Printer&quot;&gt;cheap replacement HP printer&lt;/a&gt;, which he was happy to pay for and order. I know this particular printer works out of the box, because &lt;a href=&quot;http://bobobex.org &quot; title=&quot;Her indoors&quot;&gt;bobobex&lt;/a&gt; and I ordered one for Emma so that she could print her school homework. The printer worked the instant it was attached, without any hassles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To conclude this post, for my dad&amp;#39;s computer usage, which basically involves using the web, communicating via Skype and organising his digital photographs, I think my dad will be very happy with his new Linux installation, at least I hope he will. It is far &lt;em&gt;too early to tell whether or not he will actually be happy with it long-term&lt;/em&gt;, but I will post some updates, if I have anything to report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. On reading this post back to myself, it occurred to me that some people might read it as an &amp;#34;Ubuntu vs. Mint&amp;#34; rant. It is not meant to be, both Ubuntu and Linux Mint are really good distributions, they are not &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbanglinux.org &quot; title=&quot;CrunchBang Linux&quot;&gt;CrunchBang&lt;/a&gt;, but they are still great. And of course, none of the aforementioned would be anything without &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.debian.org&quot;&gt;Debian&lt;/a&gt;, but that is a whole other story, best left for a separate post. :P&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Tags: &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/tags/hardware/&quot; title=&quot;Browse all posts tagged with “hardware”&quot;&gt;hardware&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/tags/linux/&quot; title=&quot;Browse all posts tagged with “linux”&quot;&gt;linux&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/tags/mint/&quot; title=&quot;Browse all posts tagged with “mint”&quot;&gt;mint&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/tags/printer/&quot; title=&quot;Browse all posts tagged with “printer”&quot;&gt;printer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/tags/ubuntu/&quot; title=&quot;Browse all posts tagged with “ubuntu”&quot;&gt;ubuntu&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/tags/webcam/&quot; title=&quot;Browse all posts tagged with “webcam”&quot;&gt;webcam&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>My dad is a Linux user</title>
  <feedurl>http://crunchbang.org/</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>CrunchBang</feedtitle>
  <id>70947615164a06c16712aa06224ca099</id>
  <date>1275096556</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Philip Newborough</name>
  <nick></nick>
  <image>rss/heads/philip.png</image>
  <link>http://crunchbang.org/archives/2010/05/23/dear-lazyweb-please-help-persuade-my-dad-to-move-to-linux/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;I was at my parent&amp;#39;s house last night and my dad starting moaning again about the speed of his laptop. My dad often moans about how slow his laptop has become, but just recently he has been moaning about it every time I see him. Hardware wise, there is nothing wrong with his laptop and it is quite a respectable machine. The problem is that his machine is still running the same installation of Windows XP that came installed when he purchased it, several years ago. As many of us are well aware, XP can be quite a fast OS, but after some years of use, it can become extremely slow and painful to use. So, I have offered to help backup my dad&amp;#39;s data and install Linux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My dad has tentatively accepted my offer, but I am sure he is not entirely convinced that this &amp;#34;Linux&amp;#34; thing is any good; I was slightly surprised when he asked, &amp;#34;Will the internet work?&amp;#34; Also, whilst I am probably the most computer literate person my dad knows, I say that without meaning to sound big-headed, I get the feeling that my dad would be more inclined to accept advice from a PC World salesman than he would from me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I thought some you might be able to help me to persuade my dad that installing Linux on his laptop would be a good idea. It would be great if lots of people could &lt;strong&gt;give just one example of why installing Linux will be beneficial.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your assistance! :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. To the best of my knowledge, my dad has never used Linux on the desktop before. I will be installing a version of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ubuntu.com/ &quot; title=&quot;Ubuntu Linux&quot;&gt;Ubuntu&lt;/a&gt;, I will not be installing &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.crunchbanglinux.org/ &quot; title=&quot;CrunchBang Linux&quot;&gt;CrunchBang&lt;/a&gt;. I will give my dad a demonstration of Ubuntu in a live session before performing the install.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.P.S. Obviously, in the interest of fairness, I would also like to know if you think that installing Linux on my dad&amp;#39;s laptop is not a good idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.P.P.S. To the best of my knowledge, my dad does not own or use any peripheral hardware which should not work well under Linux (read iPods, iPhones etc.)&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Tags: &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/tags/linux/&quot; title=&quot;Browse all posts tagged with “linux”&quot;&gt;linux&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/tags/ubuntu/&quot; title=&quot;Browse all posts tagged with “ubuntu”&quot;&gt;ubuntu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>Dear LazyWeb, please help persuade my dad to move to Linux</title>
  <feedurl>http://crunchbang.org/</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>CrunchBang</feedtitle>
  <id>ad4aaaa968adbec90d2a87476cdc5b3b</id>
  <date>1274618702</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Miklos Bacso</name>
  <nick>miklos</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/miklos.png</image>
  <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/memento_log/~3/iJXWMyFXQvk/google-tribute-to-pacman.html</link>
  <text>&lt;a href=&quot;http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2010/05/celebrating-pac-mans-30th-birthday.html&quot;&gt;http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2010/05/celebrating-pac-mans-30th-birthday.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://news.cnet.com/8301-13772_3-20005528-52.html&quot;&gt;http://news.cnet.com/8301-13772_3-20005528-52.html&lt;/a&gt;</text>
  <title>Google tribute to PacMan's 30th birthday</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.miklos.ca/log</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Log - Miklos Bacso</feedtitle>
  <id>fd050269d9903b65441ee752475b0257</id>
  <date>1274487496</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Christopher W.</name>
  <nick>moparx</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://www.linuxinfusion.com/google-announces-webm-open-and-royalty-free-codec</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;Google has open-sourced their VP8 video codec and announced &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.webmproject.org/&quot; title=&quot;The WebM Project&quot;&gt;The WebM Project&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new file format combines the VP8 video codec with Vorbis and will play within your web browser using HTML5.&lt;br /&gt;
It is a huge win for proponents of open web standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Information on accessing the Git repository for the source code is readily available at:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.webmproject.org/code/&quot;&gt;http://www.webmproject.org/code/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>Google announces WebM, an open and royalty-free codec</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.linuxinfusion.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Linux Infusion</feedtitle>
  <id>6abdc57d11850cc66164b2f307a6fb37</id>
  <date>1274314391</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Christopher W.</name>
  <nick>moparx</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://www.linuxinfusion.com/arch-linux-201005-snapshots-released</link>
  <text></text>
  <title>Arch Linux 2010.05 Snapshots Released</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.linuxinfusion.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Linux Infusion</feedtitle>
  <id>59519b95fd3077eeaf2330c06fd685b2</id>
  <date>1274241714</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Akkana Peck</name>
  <nick>akk</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://shallowsky.com/blog/writing/kdenlive1.html</link>
  <text>A couple of weeks ago, I shot a lot of short video clips with my
digital camera at an indoor fun fly (in the intervals when I wasn't
crashing around with the other crazy pilots).
&lt;p&gt;
But then ... what to do with a bunch of disconnected video clips?
I've uploaded short clips to youtube before, but never extracted the
good parts and edited them together. And most video editing programs
look pretty complex.
&lt;p&gt;
The answer turned out to be kdenlive, which was surprisingly easy to
use -- once I got past one initial bug. So I wrote up the details.
Part I, covering the basics of how to get started and combine clips,
is on Linux Planet:
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.linuxplanet.com/linuxplanet/tutorials/7064/1/&quot;&gt;Making
Movies in Linux with Kdenlive&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;p&gt;
Watch for part II in a couple of weeks, where I'll cover transition
effects, music and titles.</text>
  <title>Kdenlive -- the easy way to make movies</title>
  <feedurl>http://shallowsky.com/blog</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Shallow Thoughts</feedtitle>
  <id>d55d2d6acbcba439469fa2510ef9c589</id>
  <date>1273818300</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Miklos Bacso</name>
  <nick>miklos</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/miklos.png</image>
  <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/memento_log/~3/amJek5q0eY8/rona-ms-bike-tour-2010.html</link>
  <text>Here we go again! The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mssociety.ca/ontario/bike_niagara.htm&quot;&gt;75km fundraising bike ride&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multiple_sclerosis&quot;&gt;Multiple Sclerosis&lt;/a&gt; is coming up once again... Please pledge me by clicking &lt;a href=&quot;http://jui.cc/Tg&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; (or the big blue button below.) You can send your donation any time between now and August 22nd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://jui.cc/Tg&quot;&gt;Pledge Me Online&lt;/a&gt;</text>
  <title>Rona MS Bike Tour 2010</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.miklos.ca/log</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Log - Miklos Bacso</feedtitle>
  <id>62c9a2bda3bb591ed04573a16779c483</id>
  <date>1273625451</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Akkana Peck</name>
  <nick>akk</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://shallowsky.com/blog/linux/kernel/lucid-udev.html</link>
  <text>Ubuntu's latest release, 10.04 &quot;Lucid Lynx&quot;, really seems remarkably
solid. It boots much faster than any Ubuntu of the past three years,
and has some other nice improvements too.
&lt;p&gt;
But like every release, they made some pointless random undocumented
changes that broke stuff. The most frustrating has been getting my
front-panel flash card reader to work under Lucid's new udev,
so I could read SD cards from my camera and PDA.
&lt;p&gt;
The SD card slot shows up as &lt;i&gt;/dev/sdb&lt;/i&gt;, but unless there's a card
plugged in at boot time, there's no &lt;i&gt;/dev/sdb1&lt;/i&gt; that you can
actually mount.

&lt;h3&gt;hal vs udisks&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Prior to Lucid, the &quot;approved&quot; way of creating sdb1 was to
let &lt;i&gt;hald-addons-storage&lt;/i&gt; poll every USB device every so
often, to see if anyone has plugged in a card and if so, check its
partition table and create appropriate devices.
&lt;p&gt;
That's a lot of polling -- and in any case, hald isn't standard on
Lucid, and even when it's installed, it sometimes runs and sometimes
doesn't. (I haven't figured out what controls whether it decides to run).
Hal isn't even supposed to be needed on Lucid -- it's supposed to use
&lt;strike&gt;devicekit&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;i&gt;(renamed to)&lt;/i&gt; udisks for that.
&lt;p&gt;
Except I guess they couldn't quite figure out how to get udisks working
in time, so they patched things together so that on Gnome systems, hald
does the same old polling stuff -- and on non Gnome systems, well,
maybe it does and maybe it doesn't. And maybe you can't read your
camera cards. Oh well!

&lt;h3&gt;udev rules&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
But on systems prior to Lucid there was another way:
make a udev rule to create sdb1 through sdb15 every time. I have an older
&lt;a href=&quot;http://shallowsky.com/blog/linux/udev-cardreaders-update.html&quot;&gt;article
on setting up udev rules for multicard readers&lt;/a&gt;, but none of my old
udev rules worked on Lucid.
&lt;p&gt;
After many rounds of &lt;code&gt;udevadm info -a -p /block/sdb&lt;/code&gt; 
and &lt;code&gt;udevadm test /block/sdb&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;service udev restart&lt;/code&gt;, 
and many reboots, I finally found a rule that worked.
&lt;p&gt;
Create a &lt;i&gt;/etc/udev/rules.d/71-multicard-reader.rules&lt;/i&gt; file
containing the following:
&lt;pre wrap&gt;
# Create all devices for multicard reader:
KERNEL==&quot;sd[b-g]&quot;, SUBSYSTEMS==&quot;usb&quot;, ATTRS{idVendor}==&quot;1d6b&quot;, ATTRS{idProduct}==&quot;0002&quot;, OPTIONS+=&quot;all_partitions,last_rule&quot;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Replace the 1d6b and 0002 with the vendor and product of your own device,
as determined with &lt;code&gt;udevadm info -a -p /block/sdb&lt;/code&gt; ... and
don't be tempted to use the vendor and device ID you get from lsusb,
because those are different.
&lt;p&gt;
What &lt;i&gt;didn't&lt;/i&gt; work that used to? String matches. Some of them.
For example, this worked:
&lt;pre wrap&gt;
KERNEL==&quot;sd[b-g]&quot;, SUBSYSTEMS==&quot;scsi&quot;, ATTRS{model}==&quot;*SD*&quot;, NAME{all_partitions}=&quot;sdcard&quot;
&lt;/pre&gt;
but these didn't:
&lt;pre wrap&gt;
KERNEL==&quot;sd[b-g]&quot;, SUBSYSTEMS==&quot;scsi&quot;, ATTRS{model}==&quot;*SD*Reader*&quot;, NAME{all_partitions}=&quot;sd-card&quot;
KERNEL==&quot;sd[a-g]&quot;, SUBSYSTEMS==&quot;scsi&quot;, ATTRS{model}==&quot;USB SD Reader   &quot;, NAME{all_partitions}=&quot;card-sd&quot;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
According to &lt;code&gt;udevadm info&lt;/code&gt;, the model is &quot;USB SD Reader   &quot; (three
spaces at the end). But somehow &quot;*SD*&quot; matches this while &quot;*SD*Reader*&quot;
and the exact string do not. Go figure.

&lt;h3&gt;Numeric order&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I'd like to have this rule run earlier, so it runs before
&lt;i&gt;/lib/udev/rules.d/60-persistent-storage.rules&lt;/i&gt; and could use
OPTIONS+=&quot;last_rule&quot; to keep the persistent storage rules from firing
(they run a lot of unnecessary external programs for each device).
But if I rename the rule from 71-multicard-reader.rules to 59-,
it doesn't run at all. Why? Shrug. It's not like &lt;code&gt;udevadm test&lt;/code&gt;
will tell me.

&lt;h3&gt;Other things I love (not) about the new udev&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I love how if you give the &lt;code&gt;udevadm info&lt;/code&gt; arguments in the wrong
order, -p -a, it means something else and gives an error message.
&lt;li&gt;I love how &lt;code&gt;udevadm test&lt;/code&gt; doesn't actually test the same
rules udev will use, so it's completely unrelated to anything.
&lt;li&gt;I love the complete lack of documentation on things like string
matching and how the numeric order is handled.
&lt;li&gt;I love how you can't match both the device name (a string) and
the USB IDs in the same rule, because one is SUBSYSTEMS==&quot;scsi&quot; and the
other is SUBSYSTEMS==&quot;usb&quot;.
&lt;li&gt;Finally, I love how there's no longer any way to test udev rules on
a running system -- if you want it to actually create new devices, you
have to reboot for each new test.
&lt;code&gt;service udev restart&lt;/code&gt; and 
&lt;code&gt;udevadm control --reload-rules&lt;/code&gt;
don't touch existing devices.
Gives me that warm feeling like maybe I'm not missing out on the full
Windows experience by using Linux.
&lt;/ul&gt;</text>
  <title>The new udev in Lucid</title>
  <feedurl>http://shallowsky.com/blog</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Shallow Thoughts</feedtitle>
  <id>120f9bde895ef2487724e7da93ff9e07</id>
  <date>1273481460</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Lostson</name>
  <nick>lostson</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/lostson.png</image>
  <link>http://lostsonsvault.org/geek/?p=360</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;lightbox&quot; href=&quot;http://lostsonsvault.org/geek/wp-content/uploads/2010/05/30604_389376473802_562743802_4220677_3874344_n.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://lostsonsvault.org/geek/wp-content/uploads/2010/05/30604_389376473802_562743802_4220677_3874344_n-300x225.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;skye&quot; title=&quot;skye&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;225&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To my dearest daughter Skye &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;         You were born on Friday May 7 2010 at 1:06pm, it was a rainy day and I firmly believe that was because the angels above were crying as you depart from among their midst to join your mother and me to begin your life. Their tears of loss go along with my tears of joy as you enter my life anew.  It was a long nine months as I waited and watched your mother grow. I went to all the doctor appointments and saw all the ultrasound pictures and as time went by I became more and more anxious to see you. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; You seemed to have decided that you were gonna come out early with no disregard for the fact that it was too early and your little body was just not ready to take on the world just quite yet. So we spent time with the doctors trying to keep you in the womb to give you more time to develop and be ready to hit the ground running when you got here. And wouldn&amp;#8217;t you know after all that time spent to get you the best chance of this and we get the all clear from the doc you get stubborn and won&amp;#8217;t come, ahh stubborness a trait I think you got from me, albeit probably not a good one. But alas here you are now and your life begins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  So as your father I thought I would try and fill you in on some things that you may need to know as you grow.  You have three brothers and three sisters. All of whom have been anxious to see you as well. So far your siblings have made this family what it is,   and with the addition of you our family just got a whole lot richer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Let me start by saying that as your father I am gonna do everything I can to make your life as rich and happy as I can.  I have visualized tea parties in my head complete with the extension of my pinky finger and I just break out into a big smile. Somehow that seems so wrong but yet so very right. I&amp;#8217;m sure it wont take you long to realize that your Dad is a pretty strange guy. My interests are wide and varied, I like to sit and watch classic movies with mom, and hopefully you soon too. I have a very strange sense of humor and often times you may not understand it and I can almost see the quizzical look on your face in my head as I write this.  I&amp;#8217;m sure your mom, siblings and grandparents will be able to tell you all kinds of stories as you grow up of the strange and stupid things I have done. And as you grow i&amp;#8217;m sure the questions about my various scars, strange sayings and other things will come up and I will fill you in the best I can. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Well lets get to life &amp;#8211; life in general is not easy never has been never will be, but I will help you with whatever I can. There is a movie I like to watch, it is called Forrest Gump, it has two of my favorite all time characters in it. One of course is Forrest Gump, he is simple man not the brightest but his outlook on life(mostly taught to him by his mother) is one of the most refreshing I have ever seen in my life. It is very basic and simple, things happen and you deal with them. Forrest ends up with quite a life, now remember Skye this is a work of fiction, but movies, books, and music are great inspirational tools albeit fictional or factual. So for me I would say keep things simple and see the bright side of life. Do the best at whatever you are doing at that moment and revel in the joy of doing whatever it is that makes you happy. Make sure I approve of it first though! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Now life is not always peaches &amp;#038; cream though, people are not always nice and things sometimes happen and life gets tough. Enter Lieutenant Dan &amp;#8211; probably my all time favorite character. LT Dan has had some trouble in his life things have not gone his way.  But at one point Lt Dan and Forrest are on a boat and facing down a hurricane that is sure to destroy everything in its path. LT Dan climbs to the crow&amp;#8217;s nest straps himself in and faces the storm head on, with gusto.  Yelling at mother nature and god to do their worst. Some people would say that LT Dan wanted to die, I however disagree LT Dan wanted the heaven&amp;#8217;s and earth to know he was there to stay no matter what they threw at him and there was no stopping him. It was a turning point in LT Dan&amp;#8217;s life.  I have taken great inspiration from LT Dan&amp;#8217;s story and is how I like to think of myself when facing problems. I would like you to do the same do not fear difficulties do not shy away from the unknown. Let the heaven&amp;#8217;s and earth know you are here and you will stomp them down and prove the universe wrong, no matter what they throw at you, and always remember that if you need an extra LT Dan to give you some help I will be here. We can strap ourselves in together and scream away and show the world what you can do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Now I know that as a father I am not perfect and I will fail and probably fail miserably. I would like to apologize ahead of time and only say I am human and bound to make mistakes. But I am sure your mother will straighten me out as soon as she can. Your mother is good at keeping me in line, and I think she gets some enjoyment out of kicking my butt on occasion. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I&amp;#8217;m sure as the years go by we will argue and disagree on many things, what time you will be home, what boys you are gonna date, and so on and so on. No matter how bad we fight just remember my love is always forgiving and eternal. You will always be this little tiny girl laying here taking a nap as I write this. You see a father always see&amp;#8217;s his kids as those little ones who need our protection and we can be quite fierce about this especially me. Please know I don&amp;#8217;t do this out of spite or just to be mean. I love you and want the best for you I don&amp;#8217;t want to see you hurt or upset. So if I am sitting in my lay Z Boy in my boxers polishing a shotgun when you bring that first boy home for me to meet please don&amp;#8217;t be surprised. Although I am pretty sure your mom will not let me get away with that one. Although what a story to tell your kids though huh ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It is really hard to sit down and write everything out about how the past day has felt. Watching you being born was amazing, your mother and I both in tears and emotionally spent and drained but laughing and excited to see you. The emotions run fast furious and very deep.  Our Family is large and has now gotten even larger now with the addition of you. Which only means life in itself has only gotten even better.  Your brothers and sisters and now you have given me such an apreciation for life, it is unfathomable to imagine my life without any of you. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I better wrap this up by now you are figuring out your Dad is long winded although I never talk out loud much. I hope I can be a father you can be proud of. A father you will be happy to see and spend time with. I will always love you no matter what. Its forever your place now as one of Daddy&amp;#8217;s Little Girls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Love Dad&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>a letter to my daughter</title>
  <feedurl>http://lostsonsvault.org/geek</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>lostsonsvault</feedtitle>
  <id>9dbfc1cc20d8929b94914d9e90fe7a76</id>
  <date>1273423947</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Brandon Cash</name>
  <nick>cai</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/cai.png</image>
  <link>http://blog.brandoncash.net/post/579494908</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;So the Google Chrome guys put together this really awesome video…&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>So the Google Chrome guys put together this really awesome...</title>
  <feedurl>http://blog.brandoncash.net/</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Brandon Cash</feedtitle>
  <id>bdc953a514b04ae1256bb4d6d79cead1</id>
  <date>1273278694</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Brandon Cash</name>
  <nick>cai</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/cai.png</image>
  <link>http://blog.brandoncash.net/post/578787795</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;I’ve made a few key updates to the &lt;a title=&quot;Sexy CSS Buttons&quot; href=&quot;http://experiments.brandoncash.net/sexybuttons/&quot;&gt;Sexy CSS Buttons&lt;/a&gt;.  Namely, I’ve added transitions for Mozilla (&lt;span&gt;-moz-transition&lt;/span&gt;, introduced in Firefox 3.7) and Opera (&lt;span&gt;-o-transition&lt;/span&gt;, introduced in Opera 10.50).  I don’t plan on updating the original post,  but I will sum up the changes here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of just having the &lt;span&gt;-webkit-transition&lt;/span&gt; block in &lt;span&gt;input[type=button], button&lt;/span&gt;, we now have three blocks:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-webkit-transition: background-color 0.2s ease-in-out,&lt;br/&gt;     color 0.2s ease-in-out,&lt;br/&gt;     -webkit-box-shadow 0.2s ease-in-out;&lt;br/&gt; -moz-transition: background-color 0.2s ease-in-out,&lt;br/&gt;     color 0.2s ease-in-out,&lt;br/&gt;     -moz-box-shadow 0.2s ease-in-out;&lt;br/&gt; -o-transition: background-color 0.2s ease-in-out,&lt;br/&gt;     color 0.2s ease-in-out,&lt;br/&gt;     box-shadow 0.2s ease-in-out;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will also need to update the transition duration for the click state, &lt;span&gt;input[type=button]:active, button:active&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-webkit-transition-duration: 0.0s;&lt;br/&gt; -moz-transition-duration: 0.0s;&lt;br/&gt; -o-transition-duration: 0.0s;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And now your buttons are ready for Mozilla and Opera transitions!&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>Updates to the CSS3 buttons</title>
  <feedurl>http://blog.brandoncash.net/</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Brandon Cash</feedtitle>
  <id>10306fdf938ab509284c20ae9178f1c8</id>
  <date>1273254420</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Miklos Bacso</name>
  <nick>miklos</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/miklos.png</image>
  <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/memento_log/~3/RD7An4pMml4/googles-new-look.html</link>
  <text>&lt;a href=&quot;http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2010/05/spring-metamorphosis-googles-new-look.html&quot;&gt;http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2010/05/spring-metamorphosis-googles-new-look.html&lt;/a&gt;</text>
  <title>Google's new look</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.miklos.ca/log</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Log - Miklos Bacso</feedtitle>
  <id>6fa234e5134e10bd1cfa051a830e2450</id>
  <date>1273130970</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Brandon Cash</name>
  <nick>cai</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/cai.png</image>
  <link>http://blog.brandoncash.net/post/572707821</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;We’ve all seen it—you’re on a page with a really amazing design, and select some text for some reason or another.  The selected text is then styled with some default background color, clashing with the amazing design.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Naturally, there is a CSS solution.  WebKit and Opera developers can use the &lt;span&gt;::selection&lt;/span&gt; pseudo element, and Mozilla developers can use &lt;span&gt;::-moz-selection&lt;/span&gt;.  Here is an example which changes the background color of all selected elements to a very translucent white:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*::selection {&lt;br/&gt;     background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.1);&lt;br/&gt; }&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No longer does your highlighted text need to clash with your design!&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>CSS Tip: Styling Selected Text</title>
  <feedurl>http://blog.brandoncash.net/</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Brandon Cash</feedtitle>
  <id>a81f75cb4ce4497040f1c2b01534f44f</id>
  <date>1273049820</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>David Barr</name>
  <nick>mulberry</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/dpb.png</image>
  <link>http://david.chalkskeletons.com/blog/?p=65</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;More procrastination instead of doing what i am supposed to i did this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://david.chalkskeletons.com/files/pics/elob.png&quot;&gt;Screenshot&lt;/a&gt; (sort of)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://david.chalkskeletons.com/files/themes/Dear%20Watson.tar.gz&quot;&gt;Tarball&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#8217;s an openbox version of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.elementary-project.com/&quot;&gt;Elementary theme&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>Elementary</title>
  <feedurl>http://david.chalkskeletons.com/blog</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>david.chalkskeletons.com</feedtitle>
  <id>06b1483d1ff88cea892bffe022d3e0f0</id>
  <date>1271192215</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>ghost1227</name>
  <nick></nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://workshop.ghost1227.com/2010/04/isle-of-man-arch-logo/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;A new custom Arch logo based on the Isle of Man flag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;Isle of Man Arch Logo&quot; href=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Flags/Isle_Of_Man.png&quot; rel=&quot;lightbox[348]&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;Isle of Man Arch Logo&quot; src=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Flags/Isle_Of_Man.png&quot; alt=&quot;Isle of Man Arch Logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
Note: There is a rating embedded within this post, please visit this post to rate it.</text>
  <title>Isle of Man Arch Logo</title>
  <feedurl>http://workshop.ghost1227.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Ghost1227's Workshop</feedtitle>
  <id>26e4f054b4439e0b7e615dcc113469b2</id>
  <date>1270124087</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Dave Foster</name>
  <nick>m4re</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/m4r3.png</image>
  <link>http://www.minuslab.net/d/?p=193</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;Continuing where I &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/?p=171&quot;&gt;left off&lt;/a&gt; with FMCrests, I had offloaded a lot of logic in the script and left it up to the base SVG to describe a lot more of itself.  I realized the same could be done in order to properly style the patterns with fills and outline colors.  I used to have to require a big list of every pattern in the script, and then by hand sort them into lists where some need fills only, some need fills and outlines, etc.  Now, the document simply tells it what it needs based on the presence of a positive stroke-width.  Reducing the script further is always the goal!&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>FMCrests: internal cleanups</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.minuslab.net/d</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>minusblag</feedtitle>
  <id>af94e79ec0187a4e16ae84a6bb1517d0</id>
  <date>1269739071</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Dave Foster</name>
  <nick>m4re</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/m4r3.png</image>
  <link>http://www.minuslab.net/d/?p=187</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;Earlier, when I wrote about the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/?p=96&quot;&gt;Sinatra staging area&lt;/a&gt; I had set up, I had mentioned a project that I had worked on there but hadn&amp;#8217;t made public yet.  That project was a precursor to the FMCrests project.  It was meant to serve a similar purpose, to provide logos for users on a site to differentiate them.  Its unofficial title is the &lt;a href=&quot;http://stage.minuslab.net/flags/&quot;&gt;Flag Combinator&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the upcoming &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/?p=100&quot;&gt;World Cup pick&amp;#8217;em site&lt;/a&gt;, I wanted to have a way for the users to show their allegiances (often times more than one country), and it reminded me of the Enemy Territory days and &lt;a href=&quot;http://clanbase.ggl.com/news.php&quot;&gt;Clanbase&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#8217;s method of identifying player nationalities.  Next to every name was a stylized small flag icon, and some people got to make their own.  I thought it would be pretty neat to be able to have a service that automatically combines two flags in various ways, so after some experimenting with imagemagick, I created a few masks that can be used to combine two flags.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was my first real project with Sinatra, and is what turned me onto the project in the first place.  This is not a world class service (and I hope it doesn&amp;#8217;t get linked around, it likely won&amp;#8217;t), but if you have a need to make a small flag icon, knock yourself out.  Here&amp;#8217;s some samples:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/flag-irelanditaly.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;flag-irelanditaly&quot; src=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/flag-irelanditaly.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;18&quot; height=&quot;12&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/flag-serbiajapan.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;flag-serbiajapan&quot; src=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/flag-serbiajapan.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;18&quot; height=&quot;12&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/flag-swedenestonia.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;flag-swedenestonia&quot; src=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/flag-swedenestonia.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;18&quot; height=&quot;12&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/flag-usascotland.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;flag-usascotland&quot; src=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/flag-usascotland.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;18&quot; height=&quot;12&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>Flag Combinator</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.minuslab.net/d</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>minusblag</feedtitle>
  <id>4e5801a49b41259b9ae92c5a0a1aecfc</id>
  <date>1269672662</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Dave Foster</name>
  <nick>m4re</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/m4r3.png</image>
  <link>http://www.minuslab.net/d/?p=181</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;Continuing with yesterday&amp;#8217;s tools theme, today I decided to see what it would take to get &lt;a href=&quot;http://vim.wikia.com/wiki/256_colors_in_vim&quot;&gt;vim in a terminal to work with 256 colors&lt;/a&gt;.  I use gnome-terminal, and turns out it is as easy as doing in vim:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;
set t_Co=256
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nice!  Here&amp;#8217;s a shot of my terminal with the desert256 color scheme:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/vim256.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;vim256&quot; src=&quot;http://www.minuslab.net/d/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/vim256-150x150.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I typically use gvim when writing code, but lately as I&amp;#8217;ve done more Rails stuff, I&amp;#8217;ve been using vim inside of GNU screen, with a few related screens next to each other, switching between them with F11 and F12.  This became a pretty handy setup for working with Rails apps, especially as I can do it from Windows machines using Putty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This introduces a few more variables into the equation, Putty and screen.  Imagine my surprise when Putty Just Worked &amp;#8482; as well as gnome-terminal did!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for screen, a recompile with the &amp;#8211;enable-colors256 configure flag specified was all it took.  I installed to my home dir on l3ib so as not to disturb the system screen, although if it works ok renamed to a different binary name like &amp;#8220;screen256&amp;#8243; i may install it to /usr/local.  Much props to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jukie.net/bart/blog/256-colour-xterm&quot;&gt;this blag entry&lt;/a&gt;.  His instructions make debian actually seem rather easy to use (I&amp;#8217;m not familiar with it), and the screenrc is necessary to pull things together.  I still need to put my keybinds back in, but it looks like I have a sweet setup for Rails hacking now!&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>256 Color Mode in Vim</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.minuslab.net/d</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>minusblag</feedtitle>
  <id>d118678f63051934c33d2fccf03b4d17</id>
  <date>1269590744</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>David Barr</name>
  <nick>mulberry</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/dpb.png</image>
  <link>http://david.chalkskeletons.com/blog/?p=62</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;To conclude my flirtation with ubuntu themes for openbox here is Ambiance:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://david.chalkskeletons.com/files/pics/ambiance.png&quot;&gt;screenshot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://david.chalkskeletons.com/files/themes/Ambiance.obt&quot;&gt;file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m not really that in love with either of the themes, and i&amp;#8217;m not sure how well they have really work within the openbox theme system, but it&amp;#8217;s nice to have stuff that matches, right?&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>Openbox Ambiance</title>
  <feedurl>http://david.chalkskeletons.com/blog</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>david.chalkskeletons.com</feedtitle>
  <id>289373de27b54ecbdfa951a0d7e87cd1</id>
  <date>1269531169</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>David Barr</name>
  <nick>mulberry</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/dpb.png</image>
  <link>http://david.chalkskeletons.com/blog/?p=56</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;As an optimist, I assume that the reason no one really likes my &lt;a href=&quot;http://david.chalkskeletons.com/ecru/&quot;&gt;Ecru theme&lt;/a&gt; is because it uses the gtk mist engine (not that it is shit). So to remedy this I&amp;#8217;ve gone the complete other way and made a murrine engine version, and you&amp;#8217;ll need git murrine I think, as we speak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://david.chalkskeletons.com/files/themes/ecroob.tar.gz&quot;&gt;file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://david.chalkskeletons.com/files/themes/ecroob.tar.gz&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://david.chalkskeletons.com/files/pics/ecroob.png&quot;&gt;screenshot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>Ecroob GTK Theme</title>
  <feedurl>http://david.chalkskeletons.com/blog</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>david.chalkskeletons.com</feedtitle>
  <id>14ec057cbee7ba3f579a0f6a0a8833f9</id>
  <date>1269291888</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Adam Bellinson</name>
  <nick>thread</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/thread.png</image>
  <link>http://www.threadbox.net/2010/03/21/ath-esw10jpn-vs-jh13-pro/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/8930743@N02/3131483565/&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;ATH-ESW10JPN, RSA SR-71A, HR Ultra Micro DAC&quot; src=&quot;http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3294/3131483565_a35e8467e9_m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;240&quot; height=&quot;180&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Someone on Head-Fi asked me to compare the ESW10JPN to the JH13, so I decided to just share my thoughts with a wider audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ESW10JPN, with its rich, wood cups, is a beautiful headphone. It is very light and has a grip on the head that is just right. The supraaural design does fatigue the ears eventually, but it takes a lot longer than I thought it would before I purchased. This is in part due to swivel of the cups and how I can position them to put the pressure on different parts of the ears and head throughout a session. I also like how they are easy to put on and off, and are comfortable to wear around the neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I first tried the pair of my friend&amp;#8217;s, I was very struck with the &amp;#8220;energy&amp;#8221; in the mids and highs. It is a very detailed headphone with a presentation that is very pleasing for many genres. There is great, well-textured bass, but it is not the centerpiece of this sound signature. Acoustic instruments &amp;#8212; like the shimmer of strings &amp;#8212; sound very vivid and enjoyable. The isolation isn&amp;#8217;t great, so I wouldn&amp;#8217;t want to use them some place noisy. I&amp;#8217;m glad I got a pair of these limited edition headphones before the 1500 were gobbled up. I still really enjoy them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/8930743@N02/3747859416/&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;JH13, UE11&quot; src=&quot;http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3494/3747859416_462d0f33ae_m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;240&quot; height=&quot;180&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The JH13, by contrast, is an IEM. They have great isolation. (Though, interestingly, it&amp;#8217;s not quite as good as foam tips on universal fit IEMs.) They have a perfectly formed, custom fit for your ear canals, so their uniform pressure throughout your ear easily lets them &amp;#8220;disappear&amp;#8221;. Compared to the ease of taking the ESW10JPN on and off, a custom IEM like the JH13 is a bit more work. Once you get the hang of it, inserting and removing the JH13 is pretty fast and easy, though (only a couple seconds) but it is a bit more abrasive. And I always wipe earwax and debris from the tips before inserting. With the right fit (JHA has a great track record) and well-adjusted ears (only a few days to a week or so for new wearers) I think the JH13&amp;#8217;s are incredibly comfortable. I can wear them for many hours without issue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sound is simply incredible. The JH13 is still the best headphone I have and at least among the best I&amp;#8217;ve ever heard. It must be those 6 custom spec drivers working side-by-side that give me such a detailed, immersive view into the recording with soundstage that is simply astonishing for an IEM. Historically, it seems that a full-size headphone is needed for this type soundstage, but the detail of the JH13 seems to compensate for their &amp;#8220;shortcoming&amp;#8221; that they bypass the outer ear and send the sound directly into your eardrums. The first thing a new JH13 owner seems to notice is how HUGE the sound seems to be. The JH13 has some of the best extension on the top and bottom ends of any headphone. The sound signature sides on ruthlessly neutral, but with a bit of a bump in the sub-bass for low end impact that I really enjoy. The bass is massive and detailed, but it never oversteps its bounds like it does when I switch to the UE11.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I compare the sound of the two head-to-head, there is simply no doubt that the JH13 is the clear winner. Not only does this IEM have a very neutral response curve that doesn&amp;#8217;t really favor any genre over another, but it maintains a euphonic sound with anything I throw at it! The isolation assures that you&amp;#8217;re starting with a quiet background, and the music is just so clear and beautiful. At the end of the day, I&amp;#8217;m apt to say that while the ESW10JPN excels at its strong points and can be a very enjoyable can for many things (particularly jazz and acoustic music) the JH13 just seems to perform perfectly in so many ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both headphones sound great right from an MP3 player&amp;#8217;s headphone output, but they also improve with a good amp. The JH13 scales extremely well with better equipment as it seems to sap up and really deliver on exactly what it is fed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love my ESW10 very much&amp;#8230; I just love my JH13 more. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also started a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.head-fi.org/forums/f103/ath-esw10jpn-vs-jh13-pro-my-review-478801/&quot;&gt;thread on Head-Fi&lt;/a&gt; with this review.&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>ATH-ESW10JPN vs JH13 Pro</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.threadbox.net</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Threadbox.net</feedtitle>
  <id>a83ada77063af0d53d513ce352da7742</id>
  <date>1269162709</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>ghost1227</name>
  <nick></nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://workshop.ghost1227.com/2010/02/us-military-arch-logos/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;For those of you that don&amp;#8217;t know, I spent a good few years in the Marines. As such, I thought it was high time I put together a set of logos dedicated to the Armed Forces of the United States (if anyone served in the military of another country I am more than happy to do the same for you). Enjoy!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Military/Army.png&quot; title=&quot;US Army Arch Logo&quot; rel=&quot;lightbox[329]&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;US Army Arch Logo&quot; src=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Military/Army.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;215&quot; height=&quot;215&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Military/Navy.png&quot; title=&quot;US Navy Arch Logo&quot; rel=&quot;lightbox[329]&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;US Navy Arch Logo&quot; src=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Military/Navy.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;215&quot; height=&quot;215&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Military/AirForce.png&quot; title=&quot;US Air Force Arch Logo&quot; rel=&quot;lightbox[329]&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;US Air Force Arch Logo&quot; src=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Military/AirForce.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;215&quot; height=&quot;215&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Military/USMC.png&quot; title=&quot;US Marines Arch Logo&quot; rel=&quot;lightbox[329]&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;US Marines Arch Logo&quot; src=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Military/USMC.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;215&quot; height=&quot;215&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>US Military Arch Logos</title>
  <feedurl>http://workshop.ghost1227.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Ghost1227's Workshop</feedtitle>
  <id>872d37722cf446c0012ea7333f8c62cf</id>
  <date>1266675749</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Philip Newborough</name>
  <nick></nick>
  <image>rss/heads/philip.png</image>
  <link>http://crunchbang.org/archives/2010/02/20/debian-and-ubuntu-on-my-acer-aspire-one-d150/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago, I won an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.acer.com/aspireone/style.html &quot; title=&quot;Acer Aspire One D150&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire One D150&lt;/a&gt; on Ebay. For anyone not in the know, it is a netbook with a 10.1 inch screen. Apparently, the machine was an unwanted Christmas present and the owner had not used it very much, if at all. The machine was listed on Ebay with a relatively low starting price and it attracted very little attention. I ended up winning the machine for £155, which was a bit of a steal. In fact, I felt kind of guilty for winning it at that price and so I sent an email to the owner asking him if he would like to relist it. He replied saying that he was fine with the result of the auction, but I could tell his reply was written with gritted teeth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, I should get to the purpose of this post; as far as I am aware, the Acer Aspire One D150 is currently only available to purchase with Windows XP pre-installed, there is not a Linux version available, at least I have not been able to find one. So, if anyone is wondering whether or not &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.debian.org &quot; title=&quot;Debian, the universal operating system.&quot;&gt;Debian&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ubuntu.com &quot; title=&quot;Linux for human beings.&quot;&gt;Ubuntu&lt;/a&gt; work on these machines, I can confirm that they do, and very nicely too. I am currently running Debian Squeeze on my machine and everything works just fine, I cannot recall having a single issue with it. I have also tried the latest Ubuntu Lucid alpha release and that also works swimmingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the machine itself, I am not going to attempt to write any type of review, but I will say that for the price, it is a great bit of kit and it is perfectly usable as a day to day system. Having said that, I actually wanted this machine to act as a cheap replacement for an existing power-hungry home server, a role which I think it will serve quite well.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Tags: &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/tags/debian/&quot; title=&quot;Browse all posts tagged with “debian”&quot;&gt;debian&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/tags/hardware/&quot; title=&quot;Browse all posts tagged with “hardware”&quot;&gt;hardware&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/tags/ubuntu/&quot; title=&quot;Browse all posts tagged with “ubuntu”&quot;&gt;ubuntu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>Debian &amp; Ubuntu on my Acer Aspire One D150</title>
  <feedurl>http://crunchbang.org/</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>CrunchBang</feedtitle>
  <id>6dfd46e502f44d9b728d98b687eae2ce</id>
  <date>1266644754</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>ghost1227</name>
  <nick></nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://workshop.ghost1227.com/2010/02/vietnam-arch-logo/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;A new custom Arch logo based on the Vietnam flag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;Vietnam Arch Logo&quot; href=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Flags/Vietnam.png&quot; rel=&quot;lightbox[326]&quot;&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;Vietnam Arch Logo&quot; src=&quot;http://workshop.ghost1227.com/CustomArchLogos/Flags/Vietnam.png&quot; alt=&quot;Vietnam Arch Logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
Note: There is a rating embedded within this post, please visit this post to rate it.</text>
  <title>Vietnam Arch Logo</title>
  <feedurl>http://workshop.ghost1227.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Ghost1227's Workshop</feedtitle>
  <id>2d5d3f7ea3bb3a20d4f266a732a2a6fb</id>
  <date>1266276456</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Lostson</name>
  <nick>lostson</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/lostson.png</image>
  <link>http://lostsonsvault.org/geek/?p=349</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt; Well with all the buzz about google buzz competing with the likes of Facebook and Twitter a new thought occurred to me. What the heck ever happened to IRC ? You know good ol Internet Relay Chat ? Let us compare some of the similarities shall we. For instance on most of the social networking sites I can become a member or fan of a group, I can do that exact same thing by joining a channel on a IRC server, which is usually populated with people I want to talk with right ? Must be because I joined the channel. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Next say someone in this channel is a butthead and I really don&amp;#8217;t want to listen to them anymore, so I use the /ignore command and they magically go away. Much like blocking someone on a social website. Now they can probably still see what I am saying but I no longer have to deal with them. Pretty nice feature huh. Now lets say I want to only talk to one particular person, I can then institute a dialog with this person, so now it is just me and them talking about whatever we wish to talk about without interruption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Most IRC servers have a message system or memo service that you can use to leave a note for a friend, Hmm sounds alot like posting a status or something to one of these other social sites to me.  You can also register your nickname so no one else on that particular IRC server can use the same nick as you. Is this all starting to sound very familiar ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Some other points to mention is that some IRC networks allow encryption via ssl, so for those who hold their privacy near and dear to their heart can encrypt their sessions as well. Also if I want to post pics or a good article I read I can merely post the link in the channel and all my new found friends can enjoy. Even most media players have a irc script that will post the song you are listening to in the channel you are in. Wow does this not about cover all of the inglorious spam you wish to spread to the planet ? You can whoa wait for it &amp;#8212;- create your very own channel, yep you read that right your very own channel. With its own topic and operators and everything. Wow what a novel idea huh ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; With that said I have been using IRC for years now and it is still my preferred way to communicate even over instant messaging which is basically again just over glorified IRC.  So my question persists social networking ? Why yes I do I use IRC everyday all day!&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>social networking um IRC</title>
  <feedurl>http://lostsonsvault.org/geek</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>lostsonsvault</feedtitle>
  <id>6b6c20ff4ae31ceb261e78ce2f1a72e2</id>
  <date>1265964363</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Lostson</name>
  <nick>lostson</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/lostson.png</image>
  <link>http://lostsonsvault.org/geek/?p=345</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt; Well as usual on my weekends off I try to get to one of my many projects but this weekend I suffer from slackeritis. I had all the best intentions of getting to some things but I didn&amp;#8217;t. Every time I sat down I just didn&amp;#8217;t have the normal fuel I do for getting things done, and when I am feeling that way it just doesn&amp;#8217;t pay to try as it wont work anyway. So I took this weekend off just kinda laying around the house, went out with family, watched the super bowl and really not much else. Could be all the snow we are getting today that has just put me in kind of a foul mood, who knows. Hopefully this will go away soon and I will get back to my normal insane list of projects I have that I wish to get done.  Hope your projects are going better than mine, so til next time then, remember CentOS isn&amp;#8217;t just for servers ya know&amp;#8230;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>Slackeritis</title>
  <feedurl>http://lostsonsvault.org/geek</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>lostsonsvault</feedtitle>
  <id>7aaf4140ef44168b9104a4e0c83e35ab</id>
  <date>1265784607</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Adam Bellinson</name>
  <nick>thread</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/thread.png</image>
  <link>http://www.threadbox.net/2010/02/07/im-still-here-engaged/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;lightbox&quot; href=&quot;http://www.threadbox.net/wp-content/uploads/2010/02/photo.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.threadbox.net/wp-content/uploads/2010/02/photo-244x300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Adam and Julie&quot; width=&quot;244&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Hello again, Internet! It&amp;#8217;s been a while since the last update, so I thought I&amp;#8217;d drop in and act like I still have a blog. First and foremost, I need to mention something I&amp;#8217;m ecstatic about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the beautiful palindrome Saturday of 01/02/2010, I proposed to Julie, my girlfriend of four years. Since she accepted, I now must get used to calling her my fiancé!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#8217;re planning on having the big day in September of 2011, so we have plenty of time to figure out exactly what we want. But wow &amp;#8212; I&amp;#8217;m now finding just how complicated all this planning is. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yay for Julie and me! Thanks, everyone, for the kind wishes.&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>I’m Still Here (&amp; Engaged!)</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.threadbox.net</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Threadbox.net</feedtitle>
  <id>fc5129bd827669479d77fbad5cfcb702</id>
  <date>1265613232</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Christopher W.</name>
  <nick>moparx</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://www.linuxinfusion.com/happy-new-year-2010</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;Happy new year to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>Happy New Year 2010</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.linuxinfusion.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Linux Infusion</feedtitle>
  <id>5e958e18fa6206f08679ad030f3995c1</id>
  <date>1262401009</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Adam Bellinson</name>
  <nick>thread</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/thread.png</image>
  <link>http://www.threadbox.net/2009/12/08/my-favorite-android-apps/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#8217;ve owned the Motorola Droid for just over a month now, and I&amp;#8217;m just loving it. Yes, the phone isn&amp;#8217;t without its shortcomings, but many of them are getting fixed via software updates. I don&amp;#8217;t really want to post another review since there &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.engadget.com/2009/10/30/motorola-droid-review/&quot;&gt;are&lt;/a&gt; a &lt;a href=&quot;http://gizmodo.com/5396168/motorola-droid-review&quot;&gt;bunch&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ubergizmo.com/15/archives/2009/11/motorola-droid-review.html&quot;&gt;good&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2354951,00.asp&quot;&gt;ones&lt;/a&gt; already, but rather list my very favorite apps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ConnectBot&lt;/strong&gt; is an truly excellent ssh client with plenty of features &amp;#8212; including easy ssh tunnel managing!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dolphin&lt;/strong&gt; is a good replacement web browser with lots of fancy features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NewsRob&lt;/strong&gt; is the best way I&amp;#8217;ve found to read RSS. It syncs with Google Reader (like NetNewsWire on my Mac!) and offers a very comfortable way to navigate and read the news.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Voice&lt;/strong&gt;, if you can get an invite, is amazing: free phone calls / texts in and out, visual voicemail, vm transcriptions, call recording&amp;#8230;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Listen&lt;/strong&gt; is a really great podcast downloader/player.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HandyCalc&lt;/strong&gt; is a very powerful calculator with graphing, algebra, and unit conversion features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Sky Map&lt;/strong&gt; turns your phone into a guide to the sky. By reading from the accelerometer and compass sensors in the phone, this app shows what should be seen in the sky when looking in the phone&amp;#8217;s oriented direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pandora&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Last.fm&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;StreamFurious&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Jamendo&lt;/strong&gt; are all great apps for streaming music down to your phone. &lt;strong&gt;Amdroid&lt;/strong&gt; lets me connect to my Ampache instance on the server back home and stream anything from my collection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qik&lt;/strong&gt; lets me stream (and archive) live video from my phone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SwiFTP&lt;/strong&gt; starts up a simple ftp daemon that I can connect to from my PC to manage files on the SD card. This is more convenient than plugging it in.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mythmote&lt;/strong&gt; lets me remote control my MythTV DVR software on the TV.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SqueezeDroid&lt;/strong&gt; lets me remote control my SqueezeBox.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TransDroid&lt;/strong&gt; lets me remote control my torrents running on the server.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seesmic&lt;/strong&gt; is a nicer Twitter client than &lt;strong&gt;Twidroid&lt;/strong&gt;, I think. Maybe not as many features, but it&amp;#8217;s clean, totally free, and includes bit.ly API support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meebo IM&lt;/strong&gt; is my favorite IM application of the bunch. It supports all the major networks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MixZing&lt;/strong&gt; is a great improvement over the native media player, though I haven&amp;#8217;t been playing local media much on my Droid. I wouldn&amp;#8217;t really want to use my Droid as my primary media player. While the built-in speaker is quite good, the headphone output is not the best from a portable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Android user base is currently growing by leaps and bounds with the release of the Droid and other exciting new phones. It seems like every day there&amp;#8217;s a great new app and several updates to existing apps. I&amp;#8217;m very much enjoying being a part of it!&lt;/p&gt;</text>
  <title>My Favorite Android Apps</title>
  <feedurl>http://www.threadbox.net</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Threadbox.net</feedtitle>
  <id>c997094f0232526b106e7d5aee0a915b</id>
  <date>1260325267</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>appropedia</name>
  <nick></nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://blogs.appropedia.org/2009/04/20/lightweight-linux/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;A fellow Appropedian asked me about options for lightweight Linux distros, for using on old hardware. Thought I'd share my response here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My knowledge is limited, but what I've learnt:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Join a local &lt;a title=&quot;http://humlug.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://humlug.org/&quot;&gt;LUG&lt;/a&gt; - look out for days when they help people install Linux. Beware of installing Linux when you won't be face-to-face with Linux geeks for a long time, especially if you're doing something more problematic like installing on a laptop - I made this mistake, and it was a horrible time sink. Online support doesn't cut it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Vector &amp; other Slackware distros don't seem user friendly, and neither does DSL (Damn Small Linux) - I looked into it, but with only about 2 years experience in Linux, I didn't feel up to any of these choices. With more experience, and the backing of geek friends, it may be an option for you. (DSL is also a much older distro, with much older packages a.k.a. program versions, but it works on &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; limited hardware, and is possibly more reliable than other ultralight distros such as Puppy Linux).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I recommend Openbox (window manager) and &lt;a title=&quot;http://lxde.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://lxde.org/&quot;&gt;LXDE&lt;/a&gt; (desktop environment using Openbox - meaning Openbox is the lighter of these two light options). These are really nice and lean - lighter than XFCE, but nicer to use. Expect to see these become more popular. You can add them to any distro, but where they're not one of the standard options, in some cases there can be clashes (probably a bigger problem on a laptop).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; I like to find a distro where it's set up to be lean, but it's easy to use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; I'm not hung up on installing &quot;free&quot; (open source) only - I want Skype and I want video codecs. (I install Linux firstly because I want an operating system that does what I need, not to make a statement.) Ubuntu makes for a little hassle with this - you have to add repositories and certain packages (programs and codecs), and the new user doesn't know this - they just wonder why things don't work. Debian makes it really hard work for a newbie, especially if any of your hardware doesn't have a perfectly free (open source) driver.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; I strongly prefer something that is at least based on a major distro, and uses the package repositories of that distro. There's the potential for better support and in theory for bug fixing (Ubuntu is buggy anyway, in my experience, but it does have good support). It also means far more software choice. This, with the previous points, leaves me with one distro:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &lt;a title=&quot;http://crunchbanglinux.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://crunchbanglinux.org/&quot;&gt;CrunchBang Linux&lt;/a&gt;: it's based on Ubuntu, but uses Openbox, but with some very cool usability tweaks, including partial use of LXDE. It also comes with Skype and video codecs installed. This is the only distro I know that comes with Openbox by default (excluding Debian and Knoppix which I don't recommend - see below). I'm not usually a fan of Ubuntu, for several reasons including bugginess when I used it in the past - but in spite of that, it's working quite well for me at the moment, and it has an &lt;a href=&quot;http://identi.ca/group/crunchbang&quot;&gt;active&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbanglinux.org/forums/&quot;&gt;helpful&lt;/a&gt; community. This is the most promising distro I've used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Debian 5.0 comes with with LXDE as one of its standard options, which means it has Openbox - but Debian was unnecessarily difficult for me. When it didn't even recognize the hard disk on my ThinkPad, I thought: if this is a sign of how things work in Debian, I'm trying something else.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And Knoppix also comes with LXDE standard.  It's not designed for installation to hard disk though, unless you &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; know Linux. However, it's apparently a great rescue disk, with a reputation for hardware recognition - the MacGyver of Linux distros - so I keep a Knoppix LiveCD handy, just in case. (I'd try the CrunchBang LiveCD first, but if things are really screwed up and that doesn't work, I'll try Knoppix.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; I've heard good things about &lt;a title=&quot;http://www.puppylinux.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://www.puppylinux.org/&quot;&gt;Puppy Linux&lt;/a&gt; - it was flaky when I tried it ~2006, but may have improved. It's also kind of a backwater in Linux development - a lot of non-standard stuff, running as root by default (which sounds like a bad idea to me and to many Linux people), with its own kind of installation, and far fewer packages than a major distro. So unless you need to go super-light (even lighter than Crunchbang) I wouldn't recommend it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I just discovered &lt;a title=&quot;http://www.puppylinux.org/downloads/puplets/boxpup&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://www.puppylinux.org/downloads/puplets/boxpup&quot;&gt;boxpup&lt;/a&gt; - looks like Puppy with Openbox. I'm guessing it's a bit harder than CrunchBang, with less package choices, but probably even lighter than CrunchBang. I would still have some concerns about bugginess, security, package choice and maybe usability, but if you're keen, you could try it out with some help from your LUG.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Anything I've said related to something being hard to use (e.g. Debian) becomes much less of an issue if you have geeky friends close by and/or belong to a LUG. My preference though: Get something you can mostly handle yourself. You'll still need help, but there's no need to make it harder than necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So join a LUG, check out CrunchBang, and enjoy Linux!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Jon Camfield for his input at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.appropedia.org/User_talk:Steven_M.#E-waste_Installing_Linux_on_old_PCs&quot;&gt;the talk page where this started&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://digg.com/submit?url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&amp;title=Lightweight+Linux&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/digg.png&quot; alt=&quot;Digg This&quot; title=&quot;Digg This&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reddit.com/submit?url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&amp;title=Lightweight+Linux&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/reddit.png&quot; alt=&quot;Reddit This&quot; title=&quot;Reddit This&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.stumbleupon.com/submit?url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&amp;title=Lightweight+Linux&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/stumbleupon.png&quot; alt=&quot;Stumble Now!&quot; title=&quot;Stumble Now!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://buzz.yahoo.com/buzz?targetUrl=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&amp;headline=Lightweight+Linux&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/yahoo_buzz.png&quot; alt=&quot;Buzz This&quot; title=&quot;Buzz This&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dzone.com/links/add.html?title=Lightweight+Linux&amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/dzone.png&quot; alt=&quot;Vote on DZone&quot; title=&quot;Vote on DZone&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.facebook.com/sharer.php?t=Lightweight+Linux&amp;u=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/facebook.png&quot; alt=&quot;Share on Facebook&quot; title=&quot;Share on Facebook&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://delicious.com/save?title=Lightweight+Linux&amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/delicious.png&quot; alt=&quot;Bookmark this on Delicious&quot; title=&quot;Bookmark this on Delicious&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dotnetkicks.com/kick/?title=Lightweight+Linux&amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/dotnetkicks.png&quot; alt=&quot;Kick It on DotNetKicks.com&quot; title=&quot;Kick It on DotNetKicks.com&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://dotnetshoutout.com/Submit?title=Lightweight+Linux&amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/dotnetshoutout.png&quot; alt=&quot;Shout it&quot; title=&quot;Shout it&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.linkedin.com/shareArticle?mini=true&amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&amp;title=Lightweight+Linux&amp;summary=&amp;source=&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/linkedin.png&quot; alt=&quot;Share on LinkedIn&quot; title=&quot;Share on LinkedIn&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.technorati.com/faves?add=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/technorati.png&quot; alt=&quot;Bookmark this on Technorati&quot; title=&quot;Bookmark this on Technorati&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/home?status=Reading+http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/twitter.png&quot; alt=&quot;Post on Twitter&quot; title=&quot;Post on Twitter&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.google.com/reader/link?url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.appropedia.org%2F2009%2F04%2F20%2Flightweight-linux%2F&amp;title=Lightweight+Linux&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://blogs.appropedia.org/wp-content/plugins/light-social/google_buzz.png&quot; alt=&quot;Google Buzz (aka. Google Reader)&quot; title=&quot;Google Buzz (aka. Google Reader)&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</text>
  <title>Lightweight Linux</title>
  <feedurl>http://blogs.appropedia.org</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Appropedia Blog » Openbox</feedtitle>
  <id>c25a226db010133b21e8105f1c5ee1d6</id>
  <date>1240280465</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Nicolás Reynolds</name>
  <nick></nick>
  <image>rss/heads/nich.png</image>
  <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/send-fruit/~3/esfjKu4Sc_c/</link>
  <text>&lt;a href=&quot;http://send-fruit.com.ar/uploads/3010082128ju1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://send-fruit.com.ar/includes/thumb.php?file=../uploads/3010082128ju1.jpg&amp;max_width=500&amp;max_height=500&amp;quality=100&quot; alt=&quot;3010082128ju1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;cosas feas que pasan a veces :/		&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=EQdnD9PF&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?d=41&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=H9u0DL3i&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?d=45&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=aGrZx87g&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?d=50&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=uhUtfL8t&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?i=uhUtfL8t&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/send-fruit/~4/esfjKu4Sc_c&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>cosas feas que pasan a veces :/</title>
  <feedurl>http://send-fruit.com.ar</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>send-fruit</feedtitle>
  <id>7d642240e15d82fd20e1af24d69cd1d4</id>
  <date>1225481899</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Nicolás Reynolds</name>
  <nick></nick>
  <image>rss/heads/nich.png</image>
  <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/send-fruit/~3/j7-YGjYuxYs/</link>
  <text>&lt;a href=&quot;http://send-fruit.com.ar/uploads/bashhermanos.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://send-fruit.com.ar/includes/thumb.php?file=../uploads/bashhermanos.jpg&amp;max_width=500&amp;max_height=500&amp;quality=100&quot; alt=&quot;bashhermanos.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Box!		&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=SjZHRDrL&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?d=41&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=6ot5CJqb&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?d=45&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=hplkk0IZ&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?d=50&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=2uIRwups&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?i=2uIRwups&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/send-fruit/~4/j7-YGjYuxYs&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>Box!</title>
  <feedurl>http://send-fruit.com.ar</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>send-fruit</feedtitle>
  <id>6b31775afdaa4fe1d66db8c8d5d9b543</id>
  <date>1224269117</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Nicolás Reynolds</name>
  <nick></nick>
  <image>rss/heads/nich.png</image>
  <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/send-fruit/~3/4SokUDO-5ss/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;Soft que llegó para quedarse, como quien dice:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://wiki.archlinux.org/index.php/Proxy_routing_with_Tor_and_Privoxy&quot; title=&quot;Privoxy&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Privoxy&lt;/a&gt;: Proxy orientado la privacidad (ni anuncios, ni javascript molesto, ni páginas porno ¬¬)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://wiki.archlinux.org/index.php/Post_Installation_Tips#Speeding_up_DNS_queries&quot; title=&quot;dnsmasq&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;dnsmasq&lt;/a&gt;: Caché de DNS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://code.google.com/p/arora/&quot; title=&quot;Arora&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Arora&lt;/a&gt;: Browser basado en QT4 (ya tenía las librerías instaladas...) y WebKit, liviano y con navegación privada&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://unkart.ovh.org/ncmpcpp/&quot; title=&quot;ncmpcpp&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;ncmpcpp&lt;/a&gt;: Es un quilombo pronunciarlo, pero es el reemplazo de ncmpc, el cliente de MPD en ncurses. Es más lindo y todavía está en desarrollo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un script hecho en casa que crea playlists para MPD en base a búsquedas en skreemr.com :D&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;		&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=QQUvIAwu&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?d=41&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=cV2AYpAo&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?d=45&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=FjQ8YBZd&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?d=50&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?a=s9ZZptTj&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~f/send-fruit?i=s9ZZptTj&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/send-fruit/~4/4SokUDO-5ss&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>Nuevo software</title>
  <feedurl>http://send-fruit.com.ar</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>send-fruit</feedtitle>
  <id>0be2202ad8c753b3aa0124a994bd8230</id>
  <date>1224054132</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Spencer French</name>
  <nick>ingvildr</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/spencer.png</image>
  <link>http://ingvildr.wordpress.com/2006/08/25/back-to-ob/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;after a bit of a window manager adventure i&amp;#8217;m back to openbox (excuse to post screenshot).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ob theme = gehtehbox (mod of rezza&amp;#8217;s candybox)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;gtk theme = gilouche-grey (by smoon with a few tweaks by me)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://img100.imageshack.us/img100/6829/obcvsgilouchegreyez9.png&quot; alt=&quot;screenshot&quot; height=&quot;120&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(right click &gt; view image for full size)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/categories/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot; /&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/tags/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot; /&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gocomments/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/comments/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godelicious/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/delicious/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gostumble/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/stumble/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godigg/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/digg/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/goreddit/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/reddit/ingvildr.wordpress.com/8/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://stats.wordpress.com/b.gif?host=ingvildr.wordpress.com&amp;blog=230709&amp;post=8&amp;subd=ingvildr&amp;ref=&amp;feed=1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>back to ob</title>
  <feedurl>http://ingvildr.wordpress.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>ingvildr's blog</feedtitle>
  <id>967f1eae76ef9cae84c58d522e0849fd</id>
  <date>1156526114</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Spencer French</name>
  <nick>ingvildr</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/spencer.png</image>
  <link>http://ingvildr.wordpress.com/2006/06/16/getting-back-to-speed/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;over the past week or 2 i have been doing a shit load of college work so i was away from my computer alot, i come back and fancy giving rr64 a try but to my delight it wipes my whole storage partition. Looking to an upside i give xfs a try and so far it seems very fast and stable, picture previews come up almost instantly. In the process of my hdd wipe tho i lost alot of ob and gtk themes i was working on so it will be a while before i produce anymore themes.&amp;nbsp; Oh yea i also just updated the openbox-cvs aur pkg to include rezza&amp;#39;s new client padding patch, enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/categories/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot; /&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/tags/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot; /&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gocomments/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/comments/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godelicious/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/delicious/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gostumble/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/stumble/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godigg/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/digg/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/goreddit/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/reddit/ingvildr.wordpress.com/7/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://stats.wordpress.com/b.gif?host=ingvildr.wordpress.com&amp;blog=230709&amp;post=7&amp;subd=ingvildr&amp;ref=&amp;feed=1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>getting back to speed</title>
  <feedurl>http://ingvildr.wordpress.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>ingvildr's blog</feedtitle>
  <id>e7db6f2b668780ef4155c3a62895bde7</id>
  <date>1150465276</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Spencer French</name>
  <nick>ingvildr</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/spencer.png</image>
  <link>http://ingvildr.wordpress.com/2006/05/28/gravity-and-aerialsob/</link>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;Been away for a bit doing college work so here are two new themes i made today, one is based on cimi&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kde-look.org/content/show.php?content=39886&quot;&gt;aerials&lt;/a&gt; theme and the other is my own creation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.box.net/public/muhmravgpt&quot;&gt;Gravity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.box.net/public/6ha4pzqtzc&quot;&gt;AerialsOB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://img346.imageshack.us/my.php?image=200605281842541280x1024scrot6b.png&quot;&gt;Gravity Screenshot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://img83.imageshack.us/my.php?image=200605281914131280x1024scrot3v.png&quot;&gt;AerialsOB Screenshot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/categories/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot; /&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/tags/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot; /&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gocomments/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/comments/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godelicious/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/delicious/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/gostumble/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/stumble/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/godigg/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/digg/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/goreddit/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://feeds.wordpress.com/1.0/reddit/ingvildr.wordpress.com/6/&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://stats.wordpress.com/b.gif?host=ingvildr.wordpress.com&amp;blog=230709&amp;post=6&amp;subd=ingvildr&amp;ref=&amp;feed=1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>Gravity and AerialsOB</title>
  <feedurl>http://ingvildr.wordpress.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>ingvildr's blog</feedtitle>
  <id>fdfb65853f7cb02f4be41e796d81de5d</id>
  <date>1148865931</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Calvin Wong</name>
  <nick>deadcat</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/deadcat.png</image>
  <link>http://debian-administration.org/users/deadcat/weblog/2</link>
  <text>man, the guys in #openbox have loads of cool themes. i&amp;#39;ve been trying out most of them and currently sticking with the clearlooks with split gradient. &lt;br /&gt; heres the sources.list line if anyone want the package gtk2-engines-clearlooks: &lt;br /&gt; deb &lt;a href=&quot;http://debian.sshonly.sytes.net/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://debian.sshonly.sytes.net&lt;/a&gt; unstable/</text>
  <title>Planet Openbox</title>
  <feedurl>http://debian-administration.org/users/deadcat/weblog</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Weblogs for deadcat</feedtitle>
  <id>94559270b42dcdfc827748b248aeefb8</id>
  <date>1145235540</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Calvin Wong</name>
  <nick>deadcat</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/deadcat.png</image>
  <link>http://debian-administration.org/users/deadcat/weblog/1</link>
  <text>anyone installed xcompmgr and transset from experimental onto their unstable box? it works fine, BUT root-tail outputs dont get refresh and the text just displays on top of previous outputs. big problem, i like root-tail A ALOT!!! (= &lt;br /&gt; and some apps like the wm applets, mplayer flickers when i run 3ddesktop, works fine without xcompmgr running... </text>
  <title>xcompmgr and transset in experimental</title>
  <feedurl>http://debian-administration.org/users/deadcat/weblog</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>Weblogs for deadcat</feedtitle>
  <id>7684015e38a6cc59e84e9de86cd529bf</id>
  <date>1138687200</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Crimeboy</name>
  <nick>crimeboy</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://celo.wordpress.com/2008/12/30/pekmenu/</link>
  <text>Pekmenu é um shellscript que gera a partir de um arquivo de texto um menu dinamico de programas. O arquivo de texto localizado em ~/.menu contém por linha o nome do aplicativo, a categoria, e comando para executa-lo (este entre aspas duplas) , ex.: gimp graphics &amp;#8220;gimp&amp;#8221; irssi chat &amp;#8220;xterm -e irssi -c freenode&amp;#8221; pidgin [...]&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://stats.wordpress.com/b.gif?host=celo.wordpress.com&amp;blog=11852&amp;post=109&amp;subd=celo&amp;ref=&amp;feed=1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>pekmenu</title>
  <feedurl>http://celo.wordpress.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>crimeboy</feedtitle>
  <id>fdcc5db8dc81a30b7f01131fa7c98a0e</id>
  <date>0</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Crimeboy</name>
  <nick>crimeboy</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://celo.wordpress.com/2008/12/31/pekmenu-e/</link>
  <text>Pekmenu is a shell script that is able to generate a dynamic applications menu from a text file. This file is placed in ~/.menu and it contains one application per line, each line containing the application name, its category as well as its execution command (quoted with &amp;#8220;&amp;#8221;), ie.: gimp graphics &amp;#8220;gimp&amp;#8221; irssi chat &amp;#8220;xterm [...]&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://stats.wordpress.com/b.gif?host=celo.wordpress.com&amp;blog=11852&amp;post=120&amp;subd=celo&amp;ref=&amp;feed=1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>pekmenu-en</title>
  <feedurl>http://celo.wordpress.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>crimeboy</feedtitle>
  <id>0827828da562f024b8558f440e454180</id>
  <date>0</date>
 </item>
 <item>
  <name>Crimeboy</name>
  <nick>crimeboy</nick>
  <image>rss/heads/noimage.png</image>
  <link>http://celo.wordpress.com/2008/10/25/my-next-keyboad/</link>
  <text>&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://stats.wordpress.com/b.gif?host=celo.wordpress.com&amp;blog=11852&amp;post=95&amp;subd=celo&amp;ref=&amp;feed=1&quot; /&gt;</text>
  <title>My next keyboard</title>
  <feedurl>http://celo.wordpress.com</feedurl>
  <feedtitle>crimeboy</feedtitle>
  <id>36bbb60ff4db5f41fad675385fe22e7b</id>
  <date>0</date>
 </item>
</feed>
